In British Columbia students are expected to meet
BC州で学ぶ生徒は、教育省が定める基準を
certain criteria in order to meet Ministry of Education requirements.
満たす必要があります。
Here at Bodwell high school, we work closely with students
ボドウェルでは、graduation plan（卒業計画）により、生徒と連携しながら
To help them follow through with their graduation plan
卒業を目指すお手伝いをします。
Take a look at this.
こちらをご覧ください。
This graduation plan can be found on our website.
このgraduation planはウェブサイトにあります。
There are six main components to our graduation program,
ボドウェルの卒業プログラムは大きく分けて6部構成です。
the first being "communication".
まずは「コミュニケーション」。
We have relevant up-to-date communication
生徒の成功に不可欠なのが、スタッフと生徒の間のコミュニケーションです。
We use email personalized notifications, one-on-one and  group meetings, online grading program
ボドウェルでは生徒宛に個別にお知らせをemailするほか、一対一、 およびグループでのミーティングを行い、オンラインで成績をご覧いただけます。
"my blueprint" software, daily announcements, and bulletin boards
"マイブルーポイント" ソフトウェアや毎日のお知らせ、掲示板で
to communicate essential information to our students
生徒に重要な情報を伝えます。
The second component is "graduation requirements".
次が「卒業要件」です。
Our counselors individually explore.graduation requirements with students.
カウンセラーが、生徒一人ひとりの卒業要件を調べて
They ensure that students have completed the 80 credits needed
BC州の高校の卒業証書取得に必要な
to graduate with a BC high school diploma.
80単位を修得するようにします。
We offer a wide variety of grade 10, 11, and 12 courses
ボドウェルにはAP calculus、スタジオアート、物理、北京語など
including Advanced Placement calculus, Studio Art, Physics, and Mandarin.
様々な10、11，12年生のコースがあります。
Over 30 after-school clubs and 40 Saturday enrichment courses
30種類以上の放課後のクラブ、40を超える土曜日クラスを提供、
are offered to help students supplement their learning and enrich their post-secondary applications.
クラブや土曜クラスには、補習になるもの、大学出願に役に立つものもあります。
The third component is "provincial exams". The previous provincial exams are being replaced
3つ目は「プロビンシャル試験（州統一試験）」。以前のプロビンシャル試験に代わって
by two provincial assessments -  literacy and numeracy.
literacy と numeracyという二つのテストが行われることになりました。
They are offered in January, June, and August of each year.
テストは毎年1月、6月、8月に開催されます。
In addition to classroom instruction,
クラスでの授業に加え
students will be given numerous opportunities to prepare for those two assessments
放課後のクラブや試験準備セッションなど
via academic clubs and extra practice sessions that are offered after school.
この二つのテストに備える機会を豊富に用意しています。
The fourth component is "English proficiency".
4つ目が「英語力」。
We assist students by offering IELTS enrichment courses
IELTS準備コースで生徒のお手伝いをします。
The fifth "career life connections and career life education".
5つ目が「career life connections およびcareer life education」
Before students graduate students they must complete two academic courses:
卒業前に、生徒はcareer life connections および career life educationの
career life connections and career life education.
二つのコースを終える必要があります。
that are designed to help students prepare to be lifelong learners
この二つのコースで、生徒は生涯をかけて学習をして
and to find a balance between school and personal life.
学校と個人の生活とのバランスを見つける準備をします。
These are components that are essential to balanced physical and mental health.
バランスのとれた身体上および精神上での健康に不可欠なものです。
Students will be expected to do at least 30 hours
また生徒は最低30時間、
of volunteer experience and successfully produce a capstone project.
ボランティア活動を行い、総仕上げのプロジェクトを終える必要があります。
The sixth component is the post-secondary plan.
6つ目は中等後教育の予定で、
we offer a rich support program for post-secondary applications.
ボドウェルでは大学出願のサポートも充実しています。
When a student graduates from Bodwell high school they can feel confident
大学出願のサポートを個別に行いますので、
they have received the individualized support
自信を持ってボドウェルを卒業していただけます。